

CONTACT

6 06 97 30 81 33

☑ abdelmoulaserghini@gmail.com

Fez, Maroc

in /in/abdelmoula-serghini

github.com/Serghini-Abdo

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native

French: B2 English: B2

SKILLS

- PHP(Laravel)
- Javascript(NodeJS,ExpressJS, React)
- Python
- MySQL | MongoDB
- Git | GitHub | GitLab
- Jira | Scrum

CENTRES D'INTÉRÊT

- Innovative technologies
- Sports

Abdelmoula SERGHINI

Specialized Technician in Digital Development Web Full Stack

PROFILE

Enthusiastic Full Stack Developer specialized in React and Laravel. Strong skills in frontend and backend development, as well as in solving complex problems. Committed to continuous learning and always up to date with the latest technologies to deliver innovative and efficient solutions.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer

ATLECS, Fez | March. 2024 - April. 2024

- Diagram design
- Prototype development with Figma
- Meeting deadlines and quality standards
- · Applying project management knowledge
- Enhancing software development and collaboration skills

Initiation Internship

Competence Center, Fez | September. 2020 – October. 2020

- Developed an interactive registration form with MySQL, using PHP and JavaScript, including authentication via Facebook and Google.
- Worked with designers to ensure optimal user experience.

EDUCATION

Specialized Technician in Digital Development, web full stack option Specialized Institute of Applied Technology Al Adarissa | Fez 2022 - 2024

Baccalaureate in Physical Sciences and Chemistry Abdellah Laroui High School | Fez 2017 - 2018

CERTIFICATES

Cisco:

- Python Essentials 1
- JavaScript Essentials 1
- JavaScript Essentials 2